Risant Kattel

Student

Passionate Game Tester helping developers expand audiences by providing deep insight into gamers' tastes and desires. Comfortable providing both functional and statistical feedback as well as subjective and constructive criticism. Keen to contribute lifelong gaming experience to help create technically sound and incredibly enjoyable titles.

Contact

Address

Kathmandu, Nepal 44600

Phone

9814718635

E-mail

spi69dy@gmail.com

linkedIn.

https://www.linkedin.com/in /lazzy-donut-382b90272/

Technical Profile

- HTML
- · Python
- JavaScript
- CSS
- Office 365

Competencies

3D modeling

Languages

Hindi

English

Nepali

Work History

2020-06 -

Game Tester

2023-07

FARLIGHT GAMES PVT LTD

· Provided subjective feedback to shape game development by applying personal and third-party taste profiles.

Education

2009-01 -2022-05

SEE: High School

BhanuBhakta Memorial School -

Panipokhari,Kathmandu

Interests

Music

Reading Books

Animes